My name is Mr Odianaka Achumie.
I come from Anambra State, Nigeria.
This is my son Somtochukwu Achumie, my wife and my in-laws.
Praise the Lord.
I am here to testify to the goodness of the Lord in my life and that of my family.
First and foremost, I want to glorify the name of the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua
for taking away shame and disgrace and the spirit of death from my family.
I can't wait to glorify your god too.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I can't wait to glorify your god but for now, it would be very hard for me to say, "I glorify your god".
As you embrace the Living God...
You are about to testify not about something God has done.
I want you to look inwards.
No matter how much you master the Scripture; without acting on it, without true obedience
to what you have read, you will remain spiritual babies.
Tell your neighbour, "No matter how much you master the Scripture; without acting on the Word,
without true obedience to what you read, you will remain a spiritual baby".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I want to let the world know that Prophet T.B. Joshua has a living God.
Praise the Lord!
[Hallelujah]
My testimony goes like this: Last month, February, my son called me from his school.
He is a boarding student.
He said that he was not feeling well.
I thought that it was just a minor case.
I then instructed him to contact the school authority so that they could give him medication, which he did.
After three days, he called me again.
I asked him what the problem was.
He told me that the sickness was still there.
I told him to prepare to come back home.
On coming back home, before my very eyes, he came into my room and lay on my bed.
I witnessed what he passed through.
Heavy fever, cold, many types of sickness at the same time, complaining about severe headaches,
that his eyes were closing, chest and stomach pains and hotness of the leg and body.
I asked what kind of sickness it was and went to the pharmacy to get drugs for him.
After giving him drugs, he said he would try and cope by himself.
I said, "OK".
About three days later, I asked him to go back to school and I gave him some medication to help him cope.
Back at school, two days later, he called me that the problem was still there.
I told him to start making his way back home.
That was on the 5th of March, on Saturday.
On that day, I was preparing to go somewhere.
I decided to suspend wherever I was going to come to The SCOAN
to tell my God what was happening in my son's life.
I decided to come to The SCOAN with my wife on the 5th.
Mainly, the purpose why I came was to fellowship with the Church, get the Morning Water and go back home.
Surprisingly, I saw my son that morning.
I told him to stay back home, while my wife and I go to Lagos and come back.
He agreed.
We came to The SCOAN.
After two days, we left for our destination – back to Anambra State.
I introduced the Morning Water to him and told him I knew that with the mercy of God
in Prophet T.B. Joshua, it would see him through, that he should prepare to go back to school.
I gave him a bottle of the Morning Water to go back to school with.
He said, "OK".
A few days later, he called me that he was coming back home, that the sickness was still there.
I asked him whether he had used the Morning Water.
He replied, "Yes".
I asked him how he had applied it.
He said when he ministered it to his body, it felt like it didn't touch him, so he opened the bottle and poured
all of it into his mouth.
After he poured the bottle of the Morning Water into his mouth, that was where the battle started.
He said immediately he poured all of the Morning Water inside his mouth,
it was like there was war inside his body – a heavy burning sensation.
Then, he decided to run back home because he felt like he was dying.
Before he had come home, I had already left for work.
He narrated everything to my wife.
Then, my wife called me, that my son was back home.
When I asked him what the matter was, he said, “Daddy, I am dying!”
I told my wife that I had the Morning Water in my cupboard, that she should take it and minister to him.
She said that the one he had ministered was burning him, seriously.
I said that I was sensing there was a battle, that she should do what I told her. She said, “OK”.
After everything, she said that he had demanded for tea but she was afraid to give him.
He asked her if it was the last food he would eat in the house before dying.
I told her that there was a battle going on, that she should use the Morning Water
and pour it inside the tea, minister it to him, pray and give him the tea to drink.
She complied with my instructions.
Immediately he drank that tea, he said, “Mummy, there is a problem.
Something from my stomach is now coming up to my chest. There is a problem”.
The mother asked what it was.
He said that he felt like vomiting.
Then, my wife said, “Vomit it out!”
She collected the Morning Water and ministered it to him again.
Immediately, he vomited.
Behold, what we saw were seven pins, right in my own bedroom.
He fainted.
Look at the pins.
Using mere Morning Water...
The question is - "How did these enter?"
By command.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This means that there is a sort of command in the Morning Water, depending on your faith.
If your faith is big, your command will be even bigger.
If your faith is little, the command will also be little.
What is here?
Command; we call it command, which is authority.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Look at the pins.
Mr Odinaka Achumie & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Then, my wife ministered the Morning Water on him again, calling the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
“Please, help my son!”
He was breathing as if he was dying.
After some time, he calmed down and that was the end of the matter - to date, no more hotness of the body.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Come.
Boy, what is your name?
Somtochukwu
You know that you can lie to your dad and your mum, don't you?
Yes.
Can you lie to me?
No.
You know you are in a cult?
Yes.
Go and tell your mum and your dad.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Open up and be free finally.
He has to leave the school immediately and they have to look for another school.
Did you listen? He is not going back to that school, we have to look for another school.
I will join you people to look for the best school.
The school is good but because of...
We need to remove him from there.
OK. Tell us how you joined the secret cult.
My name is Somtochukwu Achumie Emmanuel.
How I joined the secret cult:
In JSS3, I met a boy who asked me to come and meet him in the hostel.
Later that night, I met the boy.
He said that I should escort him somewhere.
So, I escorted him somewhere in the bush.
I saw many boys there who started flogging me with knives and told me to lie down.
After flogging me, they initiated me using a razor and an egg in the bush.
After initiating me, from that day, I joined the secret cult.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Each pin represents their mission.
They were not given to him to be swallowed, but they entered him by command.
You, as a Christian, use the command by the power of God; they also use commands.
The Bible says, "We are not fighting the flesh and blood, but spirit beings".
Powers of principalities.
These pins entered by command.
They were not vomited like they said: The pins came out by command.
That Morning Water - don't play with it.
Mr Odinaka Achumie & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Those pins became physical pins at the time they were coming out.
So, they flogged you?
Yes.
What is the name of your cult?
Arobaga.
OK. It's all right. Forget about that.
Did you listen to that? This is the name.
Mr Odinaka Achumie & Family - Morning Water Testimony
In which class are you?
SS1, sir.
SS1.
Can you see your children at home?
SS1 - the first section of the secondary school.
If this could happen in SS1, the beginners - so definitely your school, your students, your children...
We need prayer...
Our future.
Did you know when those pins entered you?
No, sir.
But you were given something like blood?
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Mr Odinaka Achumie & Family - Morning Water Testimony
Let me just assure the father and mother; there is no problem.
Please, I want to assure you; no problem. OK?
There is nothing to be afraid of.
What we need to do now...
Look; listen, mamma.
Do you know what we need to do now?
Yes, sir.
Immediately after the service - wait for me.
He will not go back to that school.
We will look for another school.
We will ask God for direction.
Right now - he is free.
Amen!
God bless you, sir.
Assume that this revelation about him being in a cult did not come, and he is just being delivered,
he would still belong to the association and only the poison given to him would be removed.
But we have removed him from the association because of the revelation.
Amen.
Mr Odinaka Achumie & Family - Morning Water Testimony
It's all right.
Did you suspect anything like that?
I didn't suspect it, man of God.
No. Let your husband speak.
Did you suspect it before?
No, sir.
I have been telling him not to join anything like a secret cult.
He assured me that he would never do that.
Why did you tell the little boy not to join the cult?
Because at his age...
You might have seen something.
Listen.
If you are telling your son, who is in the secondary school, not to join a secret cult,
you might have seen some traces in his character, or attitude.
It is too early to tell a secondary school boy not to join a secret cult.
Why?
Please, open up.
Don't worry. Just tell us everything.
It is too early.
If he were at the university...
Even at the university, if you know what kind of person your son or daughter is,
you would not even mention that to them.
Telling your little son at secondary school not to join a secret cult - it is too early.
And that language is to be for...
Were you suspecting because of the character, an attitude or what you have seen to say that kind of thing?
Sir, in the environment where I was living before, almost all youths at his age are occultists.
That was why I instructed him not to join those boys.
That also motivated me to move to a different area - very far from there.
OK.
We are clear now.
It was because of the things you saw in the environment you were living in.
Thank you.
Apart from that, have you ever suspected this boy because of his attitude or character?
Have you seen anything strange?
No, sir.
I was even shocked when he confirmed.
Stand up.
Do you know the reason why I asked you to stand up?
Trust yourself and God.
Those of you who are ready to die because of your children; when you see "hell", you will not trust anybody.
Some of you here are ready to die because of your children.
You trust them to any length.
While even you yourself, you do not trust yourself.
Ask your neighbour, "Do you trust yourself?"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You don't trust yourself.
If you trusted yourself, you would know who you are.
You don't know who you are.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Love everyone and trust only God.
You don't trust yourself and you say that you trust someone.
You say you trust your children...
Look at this man.
It is not his fault.
He said he was shocked when the boy answered "Yes" to the man of God saying,
"Do you know that you are in a cult?"
He was expecting his son to say, "I don't know what the meaning of cult is".
When the boy said that he was in a cult, the father was surprised.
Please, learn to trust only God and love everyone.
Leave the word "trust" to God.
Tell your neighbour, "Leave the word 'trust'"
To whom?
[To God]
I cannot hear you.
[Leave the word "trust" to God.]
As of today, leave the word "trust" to only God.
Love everyone.
You may be seated.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
STANDARD FOR LIFE
My name is Mr Odinaka Achumie.
Next to me is my wife.
We come from Anambra State, Nigeria.
God used this ministry to deliver my son, Somtochukwu Achumie, from evil attacks, through vomiting pins.
He also delivered him from the spirit of death that was in my family.
Ever since my son was delivered, there has been a big difference in his life.
If you saw him now, you would not recognise him anymore because he is now very healthy.
I want to thank the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua whom God used mightily to deliver my family
and put away shame completely from my family.
Without the help of God, it would have been a different story altogether.
But glory be to God for making it possible that I would be among persons who would partake
in the blessings of this ministry.
Amen. To God be the glory.
And truly better is not good enough, the best is yet to come.
In this fashion, Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV partners count it a privilege to be able to support
your family to send your son to school.
In this case, the man of God and Emmanuel TV partners are presenting you
with a scholarship of 150,000 naira for your son.
You can take out the money.
T.B. Joshua Supports Mr & Mrs Achumie With A Scholarship Of N150,000 For Their Son
First of all, I want to thank the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I also thank the man of God for his mercy and kindness, most especially towards my family.
It is very surprising to me but I know that it is God who is doing it through him.
May God bless him, keep him, give him long life and sound health
so that he will be alive to do more for others.
It is not possible to be delivered and receive a scholarship in one place.
This is the only place where I have seen such a thing.
I did not pay a dime.
I did not even pay one naira.
Since we came here, the man of God has been taking care of us.
He provided us with accommodation and feeding all this time.
In fact, we lived like kings.
He did a lot for us, what we never even expected.
To God be the glory.
We thank God Almighty for your life.
Truly, a million thanks are not enough for what Jesus Christ has given us today.
My husband has said it all but I want to thank the God of T.B. Joshua.
I want to thank Jesus Christ who made it possible for me today to be a happy woman in this world
because satan came to steal from my house and family but the God of T.B. Joshua said, “No”.
The God of T.B. Joshua delivered my son and gave him a scholarship of N150,000.
I want to return all the glory to God.
I want to pray for Prophet T.B. Joshua that God would give him long life and lift him up.
I wish him Heaven at last.
I want to say, "Thank You, Jesus for what You have done in my family!"
I don’t know what to say; I am short of words.
But I want to say, "Thank You, Jesus".
God of T.B. Joshua, I worship You.
I thank You, Lord, in Jesus’ name.
Amen.
To God be the glory.
We have no natural words to describe this kind of joy you are feeling right now, except to say,
"Thank You, Jesus Christ".
We encourage you; you are blessed and you are delivered by the Word of God.
Make God's Word the standard for your life and His rule your principle and you will see that for you
and your family better is truly not good enough - the best is yet to come, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons, and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 17/06/2018